Danny? Danny DeMarco?
Danny?Danny DeMarco?
Yeah?
对?
It's me. Tony. Tony Berelli.
是我.Tony.Tony Berelli.
-Tony Berelli. Wow.   -Yeah, yeah.
-Tony Berelli.Wow.    -是的.是的.
I haven't seen you in years.
好多年不见了.
How are you doing?
你怎么样?
I'm doing fine. Great. How about you?
我很好. 好极了.你呢?
Aah-you know.
Aah-你知道的.
Man, you look really different.
伙计,你看上去和以前大不一样了.
What happened to the glasses?
你的眼镜呢?
I got contact lenses.
我戴隐形眼镜了.
I took off a few pounds.
我轻了几磅.
I got in shape.
体型好了.
Hey, do you want to keep on running?
Hey,你想继续跑步吗?
-Yeah, absolutely.   -Come on.
-好的,当然.          -来吧.
What are you doing these days?
你最近在做什么?
I manage one of my father's stores.
我在经营我父亲的一家商店.
You remember: radiow, stereos.
你记得吧:收音机、音响设备.
It's not bad.
还不错.
I've got flexible hours so I can work out when I want.
我可以灵活地支配时间,所以我想锻炼就可以锻炼.
Do you believe it? I lift weights now.
你相信吗? 我现在还举重.
You're a new man, Tony.
你与以前大不一样了,Tony.
So, are you married?
那么,你结婚了吗?
No. No. No wife, no kids.
没有.没有.没有妻子,没有孩子.
As of two weeks ago, no girlfriend. You?
从两周前开始没有了女朋友.你呢?
Nah. Listen.
没有.听着.
We'll have wives and children and houses before we know it.
我们会有妻子、孩子和房子的, 不等我们明白过来怎么回事.
So don't rush it.
所以不着急.
So, what's your story?
那么,你的故事是怎样?
I'm still trying to figure out what I want to do, you know?
我还在琢磨我想干什么,你明白吗?
Yeah. I know.
是啊.我明白.
I work at Kinko's, nights.
我在Kinko复印社工作,夜班.
Actually today, I'm starting a second job.
事实上,今天我开始做第二份工作.
You know part-time, extra cash.
是兼职,额外的收入.
What is it?
是什么工作?
You know those guys that deliver telegrams and flowers?
你知道那些送电报、送花的人吗?
Really?
是真的吗?
Really.
是真的.
Well. It's a job.
Well.是份工作.